Yes, we get superpowers!
Superpowers!
There's a monster deep
within your dreams Taking aim
for your heart so it would
seem Stand tall and read,
go to hell and jump for
paradise Every time dangerous,
dangerous We like it serious, serious,
oh Looking deep in the dream
there is the one in pain
Turns out that's the one who
means the most to you today
Adventure calls now,
let's go The balls filled between us, they
will show Still what we don't know Yes,
working hard together Yes,
we've got superpowers Got to dream
despite the rivalry Gotta see
it through believing in you
There's even charm in failure Yes,
we've got superpowers
All the love and the tears
in the world we're in
United gently bringing
up our thought again,
yeah We're the foolish ones
we love, we'll carry on
Till we see the light, the sun will rise
The greatest fight at its core is
against myself forevermore Come on,
let's do it now,
let's go The bonds built between us,
they will show So what we don't know,
that's what we call adventure Yes,
we've got superpowers Got to dream
despite the rivalry Gotta see
it through believing in you
There's even charm in failure Yes,
we've got superpowers Superpowers
Yes, we've got superpowers
Superpowers Yes,
we've got superpowers
Superpowers Superpowers Yes,
we're the Super Bowers Super Bowers Yes,
we're the Super Bowers
You have no idea how dead you are
Let's go, Dawn
yes master how may i assist you hunt down
that furry punk and drop her to pieces
i'll carve it into your bones Please.
I know you mean well, sir, but I'm
afraid that you're going to kill us.
It looks like you, Tia,
need to work on your aim.
That I shall! Come this way.
Like the pain in the ass!
Sneaky wine, hurry! Switch!
I'm begging you!
Please stop, sir!
You sneaky rat!
Is she gonna steal every wheel we've got?
I bet you think this is
real funny, don't you?
She's too fast and the enemy is destroying
their own fleet trying to catch her!
We're lucky we have her.
Yeah, she's awesome, right?
Karen is like a little sister to me.
When the weather and moon cycles
align, minks are quite strong.
And with proper training,
they're unstoppable.
You mean the full moon lets
her do all that stuff? Hmm.
As the story goes, on a clear night,
if the minks gaze up at a full moon,
they call forth the primal memories.
buried deep within their subconscious.
People refer to this pure,
white, ferocious form as Sulong,
or Moonlion.
Moonlion?
But the transformation may
cause them to lose control.
If they cannot maintain
their sense of self,
they'll lash out at friend and foe alike.
And it can spell their own end as well.
You mean the transformation drains
their life force or something?
Not exactly,
but if they continue to
fight all through the night,
their body just won't be able to take it.
They'll surely die.
What?
That's awful.
A double-edged sword, then.
The sort of technique one would only
use in a life-or-death struggle.
In that case, it was wise of Garrett to
steal the wheels and avoid direct combat.
I shall back her up to settle
this as quickly as possible.
before she can harm herself.
How will you do that?
You're going to fall into the sea.
Worry not, friends.
Oh, I see.
He's light enough to
run on top of the water.
He is just bones.
Let's have faith that they'll
secure the route for us.
Nothing we can do but keep
moving forward at full speed.
All right.
Not stopping, huh?
Dunge to the left!
To the right!
Whoa, stop, D .D.
Prometheus, where are you?
Mama?
Hey, Press!
Mama's acting strange!
Yeah, I know.
Oh, she's lost a lickety lot of
weight and her breathing is irregular.
Prometheus, Zeus...
Napoleon!
What happened to Prometheus and Zeus?
I'll call them over right now!
At this point, her hunger
pangs have lasted eight hours.
Surely, this is her lickety
longest rampage ever.
Ah, it's more than a craving.
It's starvation.
Even as her eldest son, I've
never seen anything like this.
It's uncharted territory.
Mama has become a lickety
beast, a brand new one.
Can we even make it to Kakau Island?
Oh, Briss, I almost forgot.
I got a call saying the pudding is
on our way with the cake as we speak.
They wanted to meet us at
sea. What? That's perfect.
She can save our lickety lives!
Well, there is one
problem: pudding is coming.
And she does have the wedding cake, but
the ship she's on belongs to veggie.
Hold on—you're kidding?
Why the hell would that
goon have the cake?
He tried to murder mama—that's insane!
I don't know—that's kind
of lickety essential we.
lickety essential we I can't
possibly trust that cake anymore!
It'll be poisoned for lickety certain!
What are you trying to pull here, punk?
Yeah, that's my line!
Are you dense?
You keep your damn poison away.
Every single chef here made
that wedding cake with pride.
Think I care?
Big Mom is going to eat
that cake without a doubt.
Knowing that, you'd have to be a
real bozo not to fill it with poison,
or explosives at least.
This is a rare chance
to take out an emperor.
And you're about to blow it over this?
Some piddly bullcrap?
Bullcrap?
We put our pride of chefs
on the line, understand?
So screw your backstabbing.
We'll win this fight with flavor alone!
Kid, your head is way up
in the clouds. Wake up!
Big Mom's had all kinds
of delicious desserts
from every corner of the whole damn sea.
You really think you're gonna impress
her when she lives in a country of cake?
Get real!
It won't be easy.
I know that much, and if
we fail, then we're dead.
I say bring it.
Even if she likes the cake, that doesn't
mean she's gonna let us walk away alive!
I guess we'll see after she eats it.
I used to wait for her.
I think I would know
better than you, jackass.
Trust me.
If you don't kill big mom now, you
won't live long enough to regret it!
Ah, uh... Oh?
Mama... Mama...
Mama...
MOTHER!
What did you do to him, Blackleg?
They're talking!
I saw that!
Just what in the hell did
you shove in his mouth, huh?
Ask him.
Uh-huh, uh-huh...
Feels like I've gone to heaven.
This cream is to die for. Huh?
You nearly died from flavor.
Whatever. You're okay.
Here's the deal. Listen.
Assassinate whoever you want.
But wait until my guest has been
served and the meal is complete.
If someone is hungry, then I feed them.
That is my duty as a chef.
Lady Pudding Why are
you collapsing, sweetie?
I have poured every ounce of my
cooking abilities into this cake.
Trust me, it'll knock her out!
Aw, damn.
That was real screwy!
Like I was hypnotized.
In that case, maybe it'll
knock Big Mom out, too.
Whatever you say, babe.
Now let's hurry you finish coating
the cake yet a little bit more to go.
Oh lady chiffon two chefs fell
victim to the delicious smell,
damn it—keep your wits
about you till it's done!
Yes, ma 'am, I'm on my way, nami,
stay safe till we're together again.
again
Gee whiz, this is taking forever.
Which way? Straight ahead.
Napoleon's signal, it's getting stronger.
You know,
this wouldn't have happened if you didn't
need to go back and eat all that fire.
I needed that fire, because you
hurt me, you traitor. Come on.
You sure are soft on that Straw Hat lady.
We're the real deal, remember?
The two of us are homies
made for Mama's soul itself.
Knowing that, your
betrayal is unforgivable.
So straighten the hell up.
I will, but I'm telling you, those
thunderclouds were incredible.
Do you even have an ounce of regret?
We can't steer the ship!
We're drifting away!
There's a path opening up. Break through.
This could be our chance.
Wow. Thanks, Carrot.
You ready, Chopper?
We'll have to fight to defend
this ship at all costs.
Yeah!
No!
They're coming back!
Let's do it!
Ah!
That didn't work, Carrot! Bravo!
Hey, uh, can skeletons
normally run out of water?
Who cares? Shoot him! It's time.
I must do my part.
Fire! Fire!
if I don't wrap this up soon I'm
gonna pass out how many ships are left
Not you, you're dead.
Blade split!
That saved me some work.
Okay, one more try.
Get it!
Carrot, no!
V .R .T.
Now die, you old rat!
I gave it my best, Pedro.
I think this is it for me.
I'm a barren corpse.
I'm glad you're safe.
I'm ashamed to say.
All I could do is put
one ship's crew to sleep.
You are amazing.
Time to rest.
You, dear, saved me.
And you saved us all.
So, how do you turn back?
All I have to do is shade
my eyes from the moonlight.
Won't take much, just a hat.
Closing my eyes does it too.
The light of the full moon
really is magic for us minx.
It was rather enchanting to be home.
Glad you're back. Are you okay?
Yeah.
That was great.
Without you, we'd be sunk. No question.
The ship was totally surrounded.
I mean, even I didn't have a good plan.
I'm just happy to help.
Can I stay in the room
with no moonlight, please?
Yes, of course.
Relax and leave the rest to us.
You were awesome.
Press!
Daifuku's fleet is drifting away!
I don't think he'll be
able to help us anymore!
So useless, lickety lame brain!
Mama looks like she's
on her last lickety leg!
They're here!
Like I promised, right?
Tommy, may I ask? Yeah! Ready?
Whoa, is that Mama?
She's light and fast.
She burned a lot of fat.
Goodness, it's been ages
since I've seen Mama with moves like that.
Give me the wedding cake.
It's Big Bob! She's here!
Napoleon!
Transform into a sword!
As you wish!
Mama!
I'm real
Not good!
She got even scarier!
What is this new form?
My cake, where is it?
Let's see, huh?
Prepare yourselves. Stand back.
We might have to abandon ship.
No way.
I'm so hungry. I'm starving.
Only one thing can satisfy me.
I need cake.
Where is it?
Where the hell is my damn wedding cake?
I don't suppose we
could ask her to vacate?
That startled me!
Careful!
If he keeps this up, we won't have a
single mirror left in the whole Tang town.
Who knew he could stand up to
General Katakuri for so long?
We keep getting reports of mirrors
breaking from across Tutuland.
Sacrebleu is already half past Nif.
It's been almost 12 hours since
the attack on the tea party.
I would appreciate some kind of update.
Attention, please, gentlemen.
I might have some
interesting info for you.
Don't spoil it.
You're ruining the Straw
Hat's chances of survival.
Go ahead, Mademoiselle Stussy.
Do you recall how Linlin was
flaunting the Tamate Box,
the treasure from the Ryugu Palace?
Tell me, is it true that Straw
Hat Luffy gifted it to her?
And why do you mention this, sir?
You want to hear a funny story?
That box was the cause of the blast.
Now you are just being absurd!
Oh, just look at him!
He's so cool!
You kick his butt good, big bro!
Hey, what's the holdup?
Is there a problem? I don't know.
Maybe I'm just doing my damnedest
not to get noticed by him, okay?
The little creep won't hold still, though.
He's so fast.
Damn.
Lame excuse.
Give me a fuck.
You know that Big Bro
Kadakuri's got this and all.
Sure wish we could help him in some way.
Hey, you guys, do you know who's gonna
get some head pats from Big Brew? Huh?
Tell me!
Isn't it obvious?
It's you, Lady Floppe!
Good answer!
I have a total of 41 older brothers.
During the Best Little
Sister Awards ceremony,
a whopping 40 of them voted for Sweet Omi!
I won!
You won't love me!
Thank you!
It's an honor to be everybody's favorite!
I'm gonna be king of the Little Sisters!
Adorable!
Everyone is dying to get some
attention from my beloved big brother!
I can't really blame them, though.
Just look at him!
Even all my other siblings, brothers
included, won a piece of him.
Honestly, I have far too many
rivals for his affection.
It's hardly even fair.
If I can somehow figure out a way to help
him, I'll score some points for sure.
I feel that on an emotional level.
We would love to get into General
Katakuri's good graces as well.
You heard me, I called
dibs, get lost already.
I knew there was trouble when he got here.
He didn't seem like himself.
But now he's back to maximum coolness!
Hmm,
despite that, I really do despise to see
him struggle this much against an enemy.
He must embody total perfection at
all times, or it'll disappoint me!
True, true.
I don't know, though.
Maybe struggle is too harsh of a word.
This other guy's really
hanging in there is all.
Every time General Katakuri
knocks him on his ass,
he gets back up for a second helping.
Luffable indeed.
Where are you hiding my wedding cake?
Let's see if you rotten
brats put it under here.
We do not have what you seek.
Liar.
It has to be here.
Believe in our word.
You shall not find any
cake aboard this ship.
So you say.
It's around here somewhere.
You're just hiding it from me! Ooh.
My eldest son told me that it's here,
and he surely knows better than to lie to
his dear old mother, because if he did,
I'd murder him with my own two hands.
I was hoping she wouldn't remember.
If you are lying, you'll pay.
Don't think I won't
take your lifespan, boy.
She's actually aware of what's going on?
I thought she was lost in a daze!
I was sure that I could lickety-trick her!
You've got some nerve accusing my
son of being a dirty, rotten liar!
Hey, Napoleon!
What's up, Mama?
Cognac!
You ready?
I'll slice you into
two and set you ablaze!
Flaming sword!
Get away from her, Jinbei!
Die!
Corgi, glaze! Mama!
The hell's going on?
Is she blocking a swing from Cognac?
I almost feel sorry for you, Shark.
You're overestimating your power!
Oh no, Team Bay! Is he okay? Team Bay!
Ma-ma-ma-ma!
I'm withering away over here!
Where's the cake?
Give it to me already!
Kara, no!
Stop it! Stay away!
Leave that room alone!
I'll stop on one condition.
Fork over my cage!
Nani!
I'm okay.
Oh, no!
The sail caught fire from Big Mom's hair!
Our dear ship is burning!
Just mess up already! Run, Nami!
I want my cake!
Guard Point!
Chopper!
Take a look at you little guy!
You're even stranger than I thought.
I can't wait to add you to my
collection of rare creatures.
You must be the plumpest
little raccoon I ever saw.
I'm not a stinking raccoon.
I'm a reindeer, damn it!
After I get my wedding cake, I'll find a
special place for both you and Soul King.
Let go of me!
We don't have your dumb cake,
and I'm not your play thing!
Duffer!
Oh, if the ship sinks, maybe my
lickety-ly will go down with it.
That's what I call lucky.
You know, if that thing goes up in smoke,
our annoying vermin problem
will take care of itself.
Oh, no!
The ship! The ship!
It's burning up!
Come, come, come!
Did he attempt to dodge?
Why aren't you knocked out?
Why do you still have
that glimmer in your eye?
Falling is shameful enough in itself, but
you keep getting back up to do it again.
Oh no, a ship, a ship, it's burning up!
Now, are you gonna mess up and tell me
where the wedding cake is hidden or not?
Let me go! Chumper!
Oh, no, no, no!
We have to put out the fire!
Where do we go?
Water! Water!
We need water!
Ocean current!
Soldier throw!
Help me!
Oh!
Ah!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Damn that guy!
Oh, that water really drenched me.
Jimmy!
Mama!
This is your final warning.
Now remove yourself from this ship!
Is that all you want?
Give me back the cake
and I'll be on my way!
Fish and Karate secret out!
Magamon Drill!
Mama!
There's no way!
All right!
He kicked her off the city!
Good job!
Nice way!
Way to go!
Don't rejoice yet!
Your captain entrusted the ship to us,
so we must ensure it's still
standing when he returns!
We cannot allow our
guard to rest so easily.
Remember, if Perospero catches up to
us, then it will truly be the end.
Yeah, you're right.
A very good point.
We must forge ahead.
It's only a matter of time before Big
Mom will be on her feet once again.
How's Karen? She's fine.
Let's make some distance
between us and our foes.
Are you holding up okay, Mama?
Yeah.
Mama, Mama.
Not bad, Jinbe.
I warned you.
Ah, that gives me a good idea.
I'll slice their ship.
Sounds good to me.
It should be easier to
find my cake that way.
It will be mine!
Her sword is stretching!
What if she starts swinging it around?
Then I fear that our
ship will be done for.
We're in a much better position
with her off the ship, though.
Come here, Susie!
Do you want some more treats?
Ready, please?
Black ball!
Oh boy, oh boy!
You like that?
Here, all for you!
Are they really? Wow!
Wait a sec, I know that
you're tricking me!
I won't be falling for that one
again, foul tempestors of evil!
Tommy, no!
Huh?
That was me.
You jerk!
Are you shot?
Since I lack flesh and guts,
your lightning has no effect.
Is that so?
Sure you want to fight me?
Soul King!
My,
how quickly you forget that your sword
failed to even lay a single scratch on me!
I recall.
But might I suggest
that you give me a brief
glimpse of what an Emperor's
Paris might look like!
Daddy.
That should do it.
Never, you mind, it's over.
Now, three verse humming.
Soul nut slash.
Our only target was Zeus this whole time.
Misdirection at its finest.
Dammit, cut off guard.
Pull it together, Zeus.
Positive charge, black ball, go!
Now discharge and you'll feel way better.
Little Zeusy-Foo. Monster!
How could you?
What is this?
No!
What did they just pull off?
They just slotted Zeus!
Mama!
It really worked!
That'll buy us a little time.
We should take this opportunity
to make some headway.
Hurry along, Brooke! Very well.
Whoa!
Tell me how much you all miss me!
Yay!
Welcome back! Nicely done! Huh?
We tried to minimize the
damage as best we could,
but the sunny still
took quite the beating.
That reminds me.
I found this on my way back.
Oh, Pussy Poo!
Isn't that guy dangerous?
I highly doubt he'll
cause us any more trouble.
Oh, what a doozy.
Where am I?
Welcome back, little buddy.
Thanks, I guess.
So, Zuzy-poo, I've been
meaning to ask you.
Why in the world did you try
to electrocute me earlier, huh?
Sorry.
If sorry fixed everything,
all of those marines out there
would be out of a job, huh?
There must have been a
misconception along the way.
How about I rephrase it?
I wasn't asking to be friends,
just so we're on the same page. No.
I'll state the question once more.
Will you be my servant?
Or will you die?
Think it over carefully, cutie.
Mama, look!
Shut your mouth! Mama!
Prometheus!
Let's go after them!
I'm on it, Mama!